<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <!-- Movies -->
    <string-array name="MoviesTitle">
        <item>Avengers: Infinity Wars</item>
        <item>Spider-Man: Into the Spider Verse</item>
        <item>Venom</item>
        <item>Aquaman</item>
        <item>Bumblebee</item>
        <item>How to Train Your Dragon: The Hidden World</item>
        <item>Bohemian Rhapsody</item>
        <item>Mortal Engines</item>
        <item>A Star Is Born</item>
        <item>Robin Hood</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="MoviesRelaseDate">
        <item>April 25, 2018</item> <!-- Avengers -->
        <item>December 6, 2018</item> <!-- Spider-Man -->
        <item>September 28, 2018</item> <!-- Venom -->
        <item>December 7, 2018</item> <!-- Aquaman -->
        <item>December 15, 2018</item> <!-- Bumblebee -->
        <item>January 3, 2019</item> <!-- Dragon -->
        <item>October 24, 2018</item> <!-- Bohemian Rhapsody -->
        <item>November 27, 2018</item> <!-- Mortal Engines -->
        <item>October 3, 2018</item> <!-- A Star is Born -->
        <item>November 21, 2018</item> <!-- Robin Hood -->
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="MoviesRating">
        <item>83</item> <!-- Avengers -->
        <item>84</item> <!-- Spider-Man -->
        <item>66</item> <!-- Venom -->
        <item>68</item> <!-- Aquaman -->
        <item>65</item> <!-- Bumblebee -->
        <item>77</item> <!-- Dragon -->
        <item>80</item> <!-- Bohemian Rhapsody -->
        <item>61</item> <!-- Mortal Engines -->
        <item>75</item> <!-- A Star is Born -->
        <item>58</item> <!-- Robin Hood -->
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="MoviesDrawable">
        <item>@drawable/img_poster_avengerinfinity</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_poster_spiderman</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_poster_venom</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_poster_aquaman</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_poster_bumblebee</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_poster_dragon</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_poster_bohemian</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_poster_mortalengine</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_poster_a_star</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_poster_robinhood</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="MoviesOverview">
        <item> <!-- Avengers -->
            As the Avengers and their allies have continued to protect
            the world from threats too large for any one hero to
            handle, a new danger has emerged from the cosmic shadows: Thanos.
            A despot of intergalactic infamy, his goal is to collect all six
            Infinity Stones, artifacts of unimaginable power, and use them to
            inflict his twisted will on all of reality. Everything the Avengers have fought
            for has led up to this moment - the fate of Earth and existence itself has never been more uncertain.
        </item>
        <item> <!-- Spider-Man -->
            Miles Morales is juggling his life between being a high school
            student and being a spider-man. When Wilson \"Kingpin\" Fisk uses
            a super collider, others from across the Spider-Verse are
            transported to this dimension.
        </item>
        <item> <!-- Venom -->
            Investigative journalist Eddie Brock attempts a comeback following
            a scandal, but accidentally becomes the host of Venom, a violent,
            super powerful alien symbiote. Soon, he must rely on his newfound
            powers to protect the world from a shadowy organization looking for a symbiote of their own.
        </item>
        <item> <!-- Aquaman -->
            Once home to the most advanced civilization on Earth, Atlantis is now an
            underwater kingdom ruled by the power-hungry King Orm. With a vast army at his
            disposal, Orm plans to conquer the remaining oceanic people and then the surface world.
            Standing in his way is Arthur Curry, Orm\'s half-human, half-Atlantean brother and true heir to the throne.
        </item>
        <item> <!-- Bumblebee -->
            On the run in the year 1987, Bumblebee finds refuge in a junkyard
            in a small Californian beach town. Charlie, on the cusp of turning 18 and
            trying to find her place in the world, discovers Bumblebee, battle-scarred and broken.
            When Charlie revives him, she quickly learns this is no ordinary yellow VW bug.
        </item>
        <item> <!-- Dragon -->
            As Hiccup fulfills his dream of creating a peaceful dragon utopia, Toothless\’
            discovery of an untamed, elusive mate draws the Night Fury away. When danger mounts
            at home and Hiccup\’s reign as village chief is tested, both dragon and rider must make
            impossible decisions to save their kind.
        </item>
        <item> <!-- Bohemian Rhapsody -->
            Singer Freddie Mercury, guitarist Brian May, drummer Roger Taylor and bass guitarist
            John Deacon take the music world by storm when they form the rock \'n\' roll band Queen in 1970.
            Hit songs become instant classics. When Mercury\'s increasingly wild lifestyle starts
            to spiral out of control, Queen soon faces its greatest challenge yet – finding a way
            to keep the band together amid the success and excess.
        </item>
        <item> <!-- Mortal Engines -->
            Many thousands of years in the future, Earth\’s cities roam the globe
            on huge wheels, devouring each other in a struggle for ever diminishing resources.
            On one of these massive traction cities, the old London, Tom Natsworthy has an unexpected
            encounter with a mysterious young woman from the wastelands who will change the course
            of his life forever.
        </item>
        <item> <!-- A Star Is Born -->
            Seasoned musician Jackson Maine discovers — and falls in love with — struggling artist Ally.
            She has just about given up on her dream to make it big as a singer — until Jack
            coaxes her into the spotlight. But even as Ally\'s career takes off, the personal side
            of their relationship is breaking down, as Jack fights an ongoing battle with his
            own internal demons.
        </item>
        <item> <!-- Robin Hood -->
            A war-hardened Crusader and his Moorish commander mount an audacious revolt against the corrupt English crown.
        </item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="MoviesDirector">
        <item>Joe Russo, Anthony Russo</item> <!-- Avengers -->
        <item>Rodney Rothman, Peter Ramsey, Bob Persichetti</item> <!-- Spider-Man -->
        <item>Ruben Fleischer</item> <!-- Venom -->
        <item>James Wan</item> <!-- Aquaman -->
        <item>Travis Knight</item> <!-- Bumblebee -->
        <item>Dean DeBlois</item> <!-- Dragon -->
        <item>Bryan Singer, Dexter Fletcher</item> <!-- Bohemian Rhapsody -->
        <item>Christian Rivers</item> <!-- Mortal Engines -->
        <item>Bradley Cooper</item> <!-- A Star Is Born -->
        <item>Otto Bathurst</item> <!-- Robin Hood -->
    </string-array>


    <!-- TV Shows -->
    <string-array name="TvShowsTitle">
        <item>Arrow</item>
        <item>Dragon Ball</item>
        <item>Family Guy</item>
        <item>Flash</item>
        <item>Naruto Shipudden</item>
        <item>Shameless</item>
        <item>Supergirl</item>
        <item>Supernatural</item>
        <item>The Simpson</item>
        <item>The Walking Dead</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>